(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
(شاهد على www.dramacool.club دعم الإدارة)
[Breaking news.]
[خبر عاجل.]
[Chairman and his wife of Blue Crane Group died in a car accident.]
[توفي رئيس مجلس إدارة مجموعة بلو كرين وزوجته في حادث سيارة.]
[Their only heir, Ian Hewei, ]
[وريثهم الوحيد، إيان هيوي،]
[is suspected to have jumped off a building due to shock.]
[يشتبه في أنه قفز من مبنى بسبب الصدمة.]
[She has been taken to the hospital.]
[تم نقلها إلى المستشفى.]
[She is still in critical condition.]
[لا تزال حالتها حرجة.]
[Blue Crane Group, one of the three major groups in the city, ]
[مجموعة بلو كرين، إحدى المجموعات الثلاث الرئيسية في المدينة،]
[has halted its key resort development project.]
[أوقفت مشروعها الرئيسي لتطوير المنتجع.]
[The board is in turmoil, and the stock price has plummeted.]
[مجلس الإدارة في حالة اضطراب، وسعر السهم انخفض بشكل حاد.]
[Lin Group is acquiring all the floating shares of Blue Crane.]
[تستحوذ مجموعة لين على جميع الأسهم المتداولة لشركة بلو كرين.]
Where am I?
أين أنا؟
This is our home.
هذا هو منزلنا.
Honey...
عسل...
Who are you?
من أنت؟
I don't know you.
أنا لا أعرفك.
This is
هذا هو
even more dangerous.
بل وأكثر خطورة.
It seems that you still don't remember me
يبدو أنك ما زلت لا تتذكرني
after waking up this time.
بعد استيقاظي هذه المرة.
Today
اليوم
is the day we got our marriage certificate.
هو اليوم الذي حصلنا فيه على شهادة زواجنا.
I've prepared a surprise for you.
لقد أعددت لك مفاجأة.
Do you remember?
هل تذكر؟
You've been in a coma for over a year.
لقد كنت في غيبوبة لأكثر من عام.
Now,
الآن،
you just temporarily lost your memory.
لقد فقدت ذاكرتك مؤقتًا.
Do you remember anything?
هل تتذكر أي شيء؟
If you're my husband,
إذا كنت زوجي،
then who am I?
إذن من أنا؟
You are my wife,
أنتِ زوجتي،
Ian Hewei.
إيان هيوي.
Has the date for Lin Mojiao's marriage
هل تم تحديد موعد زفاف لين موجياو؟
to the Zhu family been set?
هل تم تحديد عائلة تشو؟
You good brother
أخي الطيب
set it on the second anniversary
حدد موعدًا لذلك في الذكرى السنوية الثانية
when she was killed.
عندما قُتلت.
Is he still looking for Ian Hewei?
هل ما زال يبحث عن إيان هيوي؟
Yes.
نعم.
We'll let everyone know
سنُعلم الجميع
at the engagement party
في حفل الخطوبة
that Lin Mojiao and Ian Hewei are married.
أن لين موجياو وإيان هيوي متزوجان.
Disrupt the marriage between Lin and Zhu.
أفسد زواج لين وتشو.
Start our plan.
لنبدأ خطتنا.
She woke up again.
استيقظت مرة أخرى.
Still doesn't remember.
لا يزال لا يتذكر.
Her condition is unstable.
حالتها غير مستقرة.
You've been pretending to be her husband for so long.
لقد كنت تتظاهر بأنك زوجها لفترة طويلة.
You must be really into her, right?
لا بد أنك معجب بها بشدة، أليس كذلك؟
She's your sister-in-law.
إنها زوجة أخيك.
We've had so many chances,
لقد أتيحت لنا فرص كثيرة،
but you keep delaying sending her back.
لكنك تستمر في تأجيل إعادتها.
You must be in love with her.
لا بد أنك مغرم بها.
Don't be soft-hearted this time.
لا تكن ضعيف القلب هذه المرة.
Got it, stop nagging.
فهمت، توقف عن التذمر.
[The CEO and his wife of Blue Crane Group died in a car accident.]
[توفي الرئيس التنفيذي وزوجته لمجموعة بلو كرين في حادث سيارة.]
[The heir Ian Hewei committed suicide.]
[انتحر الوريث إيان هيوي.]
[Lin Group took over Blue Crane.]
[استحوذت مجموعة لين على شركة بلو كرين.]
Car accident?
حادث سيارة؟
Suicide?
انتحار؟
[Lin Group, ]
[مجموعة لين،]
[Lanhe, ]
[لانه،]
[Weiwei.]
[ويوي.]
Where are you going
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
in such a hurry?
في عجلة من أمرك؟
I don't remember you at all.
لا أتذكرك على الإطلاق.
Videos and photos can be faked.
يمكن تزييف مقاطع الفيديو والصور.
They don't prove our relationship.
إنها لا تثبت علاقتنا.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
Since you don't believe me,
بما أنك لا تصدقني،
then I'll
ثم سأفعل
prove it.
أثبت ذلك.
You're violating my will.
أنت تنتهك إرادتي.
It's against the law.
هذا مخالف للقانون.
Your head was badly injured after the fall,
لقد تعرضت لإصابة بالغة في رأسك بعد السقوط،
which caused your memory to be messed up.
مما تسبب في تشوش ذاكرتك.
Am I really a suicide?
هل أنا حقاً شخصٌ يُقدم على الانتحار؟
Were those fragments just now
هل كانت تلك الشظايا قبل قليل؟
all my delusions?
كل أوهامي؟
Marriage certificate.
شهادة زواج.
Am I violating
هل أنا أنتهك القانون؟
your will now?
وصيتك الآن؟
I know you're confused right now.
أعلم أنك مرتبك الآن.
You need your own space to digest it.
أنت بحاجة إلى مساحة خاصة بك لاستيعاب الأمر.
Let's take it slow.
لنأخذ الأمور ببطء.
I'll always be here for you.
سأكون دائماً هنا من أجلك.
Vivi,
أنت تعيش،
I'll go prepare breakfast for you.
سأذهب لأحضر لك الفطور.
You go back to your room and rest.
تعود إلى غرفتك وتستريح.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
When did you learn to cook?
متى تعلمت الطبخ؟
Honey,
عسل،
don't you want to introduce me?
ألا تريد أن تعرفني على غيري؟
Honey?
عسل؟
How dare you hit me?
كيف تجرؤ على ضربي؟
Lin Moqing, you bastard!
لين موكينغ، أيها اللقيط!
I've done so much for you.
لقد فعلت الكثير من أجلك.
I even put the Zhu family on you.
بل إنني ألصقت اسم عائلة تشو بك.
But what about you?
لكن ماذا عنك؟
When did I say I needed it?
متى قلت إنني أحتاج إليه؟
What about the marriage between our two families?
وماذا عن الزواج بين عائلتينا؟
Are you not going to care about it anymore?
ألن تهتم بالأمر بعد الآن؟
If you want to take revenge on Lin Mojiao,
إذا كنت تريد الانتقام من لين موجياو،
marrying me is the best way.
الزواج مني هو أفضل طريقة.
I don't need to use marriage,
لست بحاجة إلى استخدام الزواج،
such a low-level method.
طريقة منخفضة المستوى كهذه.
Zhu Wenjie is just the daughter of my partner.
تشو وينجي هي مجرد ابنة شريكي.
No need to explain.
لا داعي للشرح.
I believe you.
واعتقد انكم.
You said I lost my memory, right?
قلتَ إنني فقدت ذاكرتي، أليس كذلك؟
Today,
اليوم،
I want to go for a check-up.
أريد أن أذهب لإجراء فحص طبي.
I'll go with you.
سأذهب معك.
I'm not comfortable
لست مرتاحاً
letting my beautiful wife go out alone.
أترك زوجتي الجميلة تخرج بمفردها.
If she gets noticed by someone,
إذا لفتت انتباه أحدهم،
I'll suffer a big loss.
سأتكبد خسارة كبيرة.
Okay.
تمام.
Let's go together.
هيا بنا نذهب معاً.
I'll go prepare clothes for you.
سأذهب لأحضر لك الملابس.
Any news about Ian Hewei recently?
هل من أخبار جديدة عن إيان هيوي مؤخراً؟
Not yet.
ليس بعد.
Look at that. Does it look familiar?
انظر إلى ذلك. هل يبدو مألوفاً؟
You.
أنت.
I want to go see
أريد أن أذهب لأرى
the ward I stayed in before.
الجناح الذي أقمت فيه سابقاً.
Do you remember anything?
هل تتذكر أي شيء؟
Do you remember?
هل تذكر؟
Don't touch me.
لا تلمسني.
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
I didn't expect you to lose your memory completely.
لم أتوقع أن تفقد ذاكرتك تماماً.
[You even forgot your own home.]
[حتى أنك نسيت منزلك.]
Go home first.
اذهب إلى المنزل أولاً.
I'll pick you up later.
سآتي لأخذك لاحقاً.
Send someone to Senyuan Hospital
أرسل شخصًا إلى مستشفى سنيوان
to erase Ian Hewei's visit today.
لمحو زيارة إيان هيوي اليوم.
Hello, Mr. Lin.
مرحباً، سيد لين.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Did you take care of it at the hospital?
هل قمت بمعالجته في المستشفى؟
You can trust me.
يمكنك الوثوق بي.
[Don't let love cloud your judgment.]
[لا تدع الحب يُعمي بصيرتك.]
[This is the critical moment for revenge.]
[هذه هي اللحظة الحاسمة للانتقام.]
[Don't forget how your parents died.]
[لا تنس كيف مات والداك.]
[To get revenge, ]
[للانتقام،]
[you've endured so much to get this far.]
لقد تحملت الكثير لتصل إلى هذه المرحلة.